<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin>
<idea-plugin url="http://www.ivyidea.org">
    <name>IvyIDEA</name>
    <description><![CDATA[Resolves module dependencies through Ivy (Fork of IvyIdea plugin by Guy Mahieu)
        <p>Features:
            <ul>
                <li>Apache Ivy integration (up to v2.4.0); no need for external ant build scripts to be called</li>
                <li>Automatic ivy configuration of modules using facets (for modules containing an ivy.xml file)</li>
                <li>Detection of dependencies that are really other intellij modules in the same project; these are added as module references</li>
                <li>Detect source/document/jar type ivy artifacts in dependencies and add them as such to the module</li>
                <li>Creation of a module library with all resolved ivy dependencies</li>
                <li>Ivy configurations that need to be resolved can be chosen for each module</li>
                <li>Properties can be injected into the ivy resolve process</li>
            </ul>
        </p>]]>
    </description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <p>
            <strong>1.0.20</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed issue with NPE when retrieving the console window</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.19</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Updated plugin to be compatible with IntelliJ 2021.1</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.18</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Reverted changes to internal logging that caused intermittent NPE on latest version of IntelliJ.</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.17</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Disable indexing while updating IntelliJ module dependencies.</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.16</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Added log statement before starting resolution to make it more apparent where errors belong.</li>
                <li>Continue resolving all modules even when dependency error is encountered in one module.</li>
                <li>Summary of errors will be displayed after resolution is done.</li>
                <li>Allow the console to be visible during indexing.</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.15</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Improve feedback during resolution. Progress will not be reflected both in the console and in the indicator at the bottom.</li>
                <li>Allow for relative paths for settings files if they are inside the project folder</li>
                <li>Attempt to match Ivy configuration name with intelliJ dependency scope. (Beware of difference in transitivity)</li>
                <li>When resolving all modules only resolve for loaded modules</li>
                <li>Better resilience towards missing ivy files, so it is properly reported.</li>
                <li>Updating IntelliJ project dependencies is no longer done in parallel to avoid issues on projects with many modules.</li>
                <li>Reuse ivy instance when settings are identical to improve performance</li>
                <li>Refactored some of the resolution code to make reuse possible.</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.14</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>When trying to resolve dependencies without an Ivy settings file, an IllegalArgumentException 
				    was thrown when clicking on the 'Open Project Settings' link</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.13</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>The IvyIDEA settings window was no longer visible in IntelliJ 2016.1</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.12</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>The configurations to resolve are now stored alphabetically in the .iml file</li>
                <li>Modified files are now saved before starting to resolve the dependencies</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.11</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 11</li>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.4.0 (including dependencies)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.10</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13.1</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.9</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Added an extra configuration option to always attach the source/javadoc artifacts, even when
                    they aren't selected by an Ivy configuration.</li>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13.1</li>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.4.0-rc1 (including dependencies)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.8</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13.0.2 EAP (build 133.609)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.7</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13</li>
                <li>Fixed issue with resolving dependencies of a single module if another module had an incorrect ivy file</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.6</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Fixed issue with the 'Only resolve specific ivy configurations'-option on the IvyIDEA facet page</li>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13 beta1 (build 132.947)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.5</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Improved resolving dependencies in the background</li>
                <li>Added an extra configuration option to always resolve in the background</li>
                <li>Resolving dependencies can now be canceled</li>
                <li>Fixed problem parsing ivy.xml files extending others</li>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issue with IntelliJ 13 EAP (build 130.1619)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.4</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.3.0 (including dependencies)</li>
                <li>Added some extra resolve options to the project settings</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.3</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.3.0-rc2 (including dependencies)</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.2</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.3.0-rc1 (including dependencies)</li>
                <li>Fixed issue when loading properties files containing cyclic properties</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0.1</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Bugfix: it was not possible to use the default Ivy settings</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>1.0</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Added support for 'mar' artifact types (Axis module archives)</li>
                <li>Fixed compatibility issues with IntelliJ 11</li>
                <li>Fixed problem on Windows when the case of the ivy-cache path didn't match the case on disk</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>0.9</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Upgraded internal Apache Ivy to 2.2.0 (including dependencies)</li>
                <li>Support for using ${} style properties in ivy and ivysettings files</li>
                <li>Improved lookup method for artifacts; now useOrigin="true" will also be supported.</li>
                <li>Resolved config names are now listed in the IvyIDEA console</li>
                <li>Resolved library names can now contain the module and or configuration name (with help from wajiii).</li>
                <li>Configurable log level for ivy logging (with help from wajiii)</li>
                <li>Dependencies are now added to the module library with a relative path</li>
                <li>The types used for classes/sources/javadoc artifacts is now configurable</li>
                <li>Several small fixes and improvements</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>0.8</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>Upgraded internal ivy to 2.0.0rc2</li>
                <li>Improved exception handling</li>
            </ul>
            <strong>0.7-alpha</strong>
            <ul>
                <li>IvyIDEA is now compatible with IntelliJ 8.0 (and will run on previous versions as well)</li>
                <li>Switched to JDK 1.5 so the plugin will also run on mac os</li>
                <li>Made looking up intellij module dependencies more lenient; now the revision is ignored when
                    identifying dependencies as existing intellij modules rather than jars</li>
            </ul>
        </p>]]>
    </change-notes>
    <version>1.0.20</version>
    <vendor email="GadeSoftware@gmail.com">Jacob Gade</vendor>
    <idea-version since-build="201.6668.113"/>
    <actions>
        <group id="IvyIDEA.Menu" text="IvyIDEA" description="Resolve module dependencies using Ivy"
               popup="true">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ProjectViewPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="first"/>
            <separator/>
            <action id="org.clarent.ivyidea.ResolveForActiveModuleAction"
                    class="org.clarent.ivyidea.ResolveForActiveModuleAction" text="Resolve for active module"
                    description="Resolve dependencies for the active module">
            </action>
            <action id="org.clarent.ivyidea.ResolveForAllModulesAction"
                    class="org.clarent.ivyidea.ResolveForAllModulesAction" text="Resolve for all modules"
                    description="Resolve dependencies for all modules">
            </action>
            <separator/>
            <action id="org.clarent.ivyidea.RemoveAllIvyIdeaModuleLibrariesAction"
                    class="org.clarent.ivyidea.RemoveAllIvyIdeaModuleLibrariesAction"
                    text="Remove all resolved libraries"
                    description="Remove all module libraries generated by IvyIDEA."/>
        </group>
    </actions>
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <facetType implementation="org.clarent.ivyidea.intellij.facet.IvyIdeaFacetType"/>
        <framework.detector implementation="org.clarent.ivyidea.intellij.facet.IvyIdeaFacetDetector"/>
		<projectConfigurable id="IvyIDEA.ProjectSettings.Configurable"
							 instance="org.clarent.ivyidea.intellij.ui.IvyIdeaProjectSettingsComponent"
							 displayName="IvyIDEA" />
        <toolWindow id="IvyIDEA" icon="/ivyidea13.png" anchor="bottom"
                    factoryClass="org.clarent.ivyidea.intellij.IvyIdeaToolWindowFactory"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
